what more do we know at this point
so what we know is that fwd was planning
to launch its u.s ipo as soon as this
week but that's now full of facing
delays and quite likely it's looking
increasingly unlikely sorry that it's
going to happen
this year a final decision has yet to be
made but essentially they're weighing um
not going ahead with the us ipo given
that there's been increasing scrutiny
from the u.s securities and exchange
commission
as well as there's been some pushback
from investors on the targeted valuation
so the sec has been asking the company
lots of questions and it hasn't sort of
received the final approval yet in time
for its planned launch um some of the
questions concern for example the
potential reach of the chinese
government over its operations and this
comes as the sec has been asking lots of
questions from chinese companies who are
looking to list in the u.s
about the regulatory risks they face
from china in the wake of the crackdown
that we've seen which has
affected essentially loads of companies
at one point cost a route of a trillion
dollars
and also caused a complete halt
essentially in the flow of chinese
companies to new york
and what does that tell you then about
just overall sentiment towards just hong
kong companies i understand maybe given
the tensions that maybe chinese
companies would be facing this
regulatory scrutiny but is this likely
to spread to more hong kong companies
that are interested in enlisting in the
us now
it certainly suggests that what we have
seen and this is um from fwd and some
other hong kong companies such as amt
digital that have been looking to do u.s
ipos they began making changes to their
filings for u.s ipos
and they were flagging the potential
regulatory risks from china despite the
fact that they have little to no
substantive operations in the mainland
so this is certainly a sign that
a the sec is asking them to disclose
risks
a lot more clearly a lot more
prominently but also that there's a lot
of uncertainty about what this overhaul
that we're seeing in china actually
means for hong kong companies as well
and certainly there's a lot of investor
pushback a lot of investor
hesitation around investing in these
companies given what's going on